A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Projects, International Relations, RG 1.3, Series 155 FA388A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- International Relations, 1971-1989; 155
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XVII): Working Papers, Nos. 81-87, 1980-1981 (Box 96, Folder 993)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XVIII): Working Papers, Nos. 88-96, 1979-1981 (Box 96, Folder 994)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XIX): Working Papers, Nos. 97-102, 1980-1981 (Box 96, Folder 995)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XX): Working Papers, Nos. 103-107, 1980-1981 (Box 96, Folder 996)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXI): Working Papers, Nos. 108-114, 1980-1981 (Box 97, Folder 997)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXII): Working Papers, Nos. 115-119, 1981-1982 (Box 97, Folder 998)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXIII): Working Papers, Nos. 120-125, 127-128, 1982-1983 (Box 97, Folder 999)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXIV): Working Papers, Nos. 129-135, 1983 (Box 97, Folder 1000)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXV): Working Papers, Nos. 136-142, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 1001)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXVI): Working Papers, Nos. 143-147, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 1002)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXVII): Working Papers, Nos. 148-155, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 1003)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXVIII): Working Papers, Nos. 156-162, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 1004)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXIX): Working Papers, Nos. 163-167, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1005)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXX): Working Papers, No. 168, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1006)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXXI): "Focus: Caribbean", essays 1-5, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1007)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXXII): "Focus: Caribbean", essays 6-11, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1008)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Supplementary Material (XXXIII): "The Americas at the Crossroads", Report of the Inter-American Dialogue, 1983 April (Box 98, Folder 1009)
  - Smithsonian Institution: Wilson International Center for Scholars: Inter-American Relations: Conferences, 1982-1983, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1010)
  - Social Science Research Council: Soviet Foreign Policy, 1984-1987, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1011)
  - Society for International Development: North South Roundtable, 1983-1986, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1012)
  - Society for International Development: North South Roundtable: Supplementary Material, 1983-1985, no date (Box 99, Folder 1013)
  - (489) – South African Council of Churches: Educational Opportunities Council, 1982 July-1983 August, 1990 (Box 99, Folder 1014)
  - (489) – South African Council of Churches: Educational Opportunities Council, 1983 October-1984 August (Box 99, Folder 1015)
  - (489) – South African Council of Churches: Educational Opportunities Council, 1985 January-1987 January (Box 99, Folder 1016)
  - (489) – Southern African Catholic Bishops' Conference: DESCOM (Detainees Support Committee), 1986-1990, 1992 (Box 100, Folder 1017)
  - (489) – Southern African Catholic Bishops' Conference: New Nation Staff, 1985-1990 (Box 100, Folder 1018)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China: Front of File and Evaluation, 1974, 1976-1977, 1979, 1982, 1984 (Box 100, Folder 1019)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China, 1974-1980 (Box 100, Folder 1020)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China: Supplementary Material (I): "China's Energy Policies and Resource Development", 1976 June (Box 100, Folder 1021)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China: Supplementary Material (II): "Developments in PRC Science and Technology Policy", 1978 January-March (Box 100, Folder 1022)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China: Supplementary Material (III): Report of a Visit to the People's Republic of China by the Stanford International Security and Arms Control Group, 1978 July 10-19 (Box 100, Folder 1023)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China: Supplementary Material (IV): "International Relations Research and Training in the People's Republic of China", 1982 February (Box 100, Folder 1024)
  - Stanford University: Arms Control with China: Supplementary Material (V): China-United States Comprehensive Security: Report of a Meeting, 1982 March (Box 100, Folder 1025)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Front of File, 1980, 1983, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 1026)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars, 1980 January-1981 March (Box 100, Folder 1027)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars, 1981 April-1982 August (Box 101, Folder 1028)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars, 1982 September-November (Box 101, Folder 1029)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars, 1983 February-1985 February (Box 101, Folder 1030)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Supplementary Material (I): Annual Reports, 1982-1984 (Box 101, Folder 1031)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Supplementary Material (II): "Japan and the World Energy Problem", 1980 July (Box 101, Folder 1032)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Supplementary Material (III): "United States Security Relationships with Northeast Asia", 1982 March 12 (Box 101, Folder 1033)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Supplementary Material (IV): "Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces in Europe: Issues and Approaches", 1982 April 13 (Box 101, Folder 1034)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Supplementary Material (V): "The Security Challenge in Northeast Asia: Report of a Conference", pp. 1-84, 1982 November (Box 101, Folder 1035)
  - Stanford University: Chinese Scholars: Supplementary Material (VI): "The Security Challenge in Northeast Asia: Report of a Conference", pp. 85-149, 1982 November (Box 101, Folder 1036)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations: Front of File, 1980-1981, 1984-1986, no date (Box 101, Folder 1037)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations, 1979 December-1980 October (Box 101, Folder 1038)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations, 1980 November-December (Box 101, Folder 1039)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations, 1981 January-September (Box 102, Folder 1040)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations, 1982-1983 (Box 102, Folder 1041)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations, 1984 (Box 102, Folder 1042)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations, 1985 (Box 102, Folder 1043)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (I): "Lecturas 43, Las relaciones México Estados Unidos", 1981 (Box 102, Folder 1044)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (II): Working Papers, Nos. 4, 6, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 1045)
  - Stanford University: United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (III): "U. S.-Mexico Relations: Economic and Social Aspects", 1983 (Box 102, Folder 1046)
  - TransAfrica Forum: African Writers: Front of File, 1983-1987, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1047)
  - TransAfrica Forum: African Writers, 1982 February-1983 July (Box 103, Folder 1048)
  - TransAfrica Forum: African Writers, 1984 June-1987 February (Box 103, Folder 1049)
  - Gregory F. Treverton: Front of File, 1981, 1983, 1985-1987 (Box 103, Folder 1050)
  - Gregory F. Treverton, 1981 April-1982 September (Box 103, Folder 1051)
  - Gregory F. Treverton, 1982 October-1986 March/April (Box 103, Folder 1052)
  - Trilateral Commission: Asian Security: Front of File, 1984, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1053)
  - Trilateral Commission: Asian Security, 1984-1985 (Box 103, Folder 1054)
  - Trilateral Commission: Asian Security: Supplementary Material (I): The Trilateral Commission Tokyo Plenary Meeting, April 21-23, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 1055)
  - Trilateral Commission: Asian Security: Supplementary Material (II): "East Asian Security and the Trilateral Countries", by Masashi Nishihara, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 1056)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: Ithuseng Community Health Centre: Front of File, 1984, 1986, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 1057)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: Ithuseng Community Health Centre, 1982-1985 January (Box 103, Folder 1058)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: Ithuseng Community Health Centre, 1985 June-September (Box 104, Folder 1059)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: Ithuseng Community Health Centre, 1986 January-February (Box 104, Folder 1060)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: Ithuseng Community Health Centre, 1986 June-December (Box 104, Folder 1061)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: B. C. Witbooi: Front of File, 1983-1984, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 1062)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: B. C. Witbooi, 1984 April-1985 September (Box 104, Folder 1063)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: B. C. Witbooi, 1986 February-1987 December (Box 104, Folder 1064)
  - (489) – Trust for Christian Outreach and Education: B. C. Witbooi, 1988 January-September (Box 104, Folder 1065)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy: Front of File and Evaluation, 1978-1982 (Box 105, Folder 1066)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy, 1978 March-November (Box 105, Folder 1067)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy, 1979 March-1981 November (Box 105, Folder 1068)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (I): "Administrative and Management Aspects of Energy Policy Formulation in LDCS" - Conceptual Problem Areas and Four Country Case Studies (Colombia, Korea, Kenya, Philippines), no date (Box 105, Folder 1069)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (II): Country Case Study - Colombia, no date (Box 105, Folder 1070)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (III): Country Case Study - Korea, no date (Box 105, Folder 1071)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (IV): Country Case Study - Kenya, no date (Box 105, Folder 1072)
  - Tufts University: Energy Policy: Supplementary Material (V): Country Case Study - The Philippines, no date (Box 105, Folder 1073)
  - Tufts University: Thailand Conference: Front of File and Evaluation, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 1074)
  - Tufts University: Thailand Conference, 1982 May-September (Box 105, Folder 1075)
  - Tufts University: Thailand Conference, 1982 October-December (Box 105, Folder 1076)
  - Tufts University: Thailand Conference, 1983 May-1985 January (Box 105, Folder 1077)
  - (489) – Ukawaziswa Trust: Journalism Training: Front of File, 1986, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 1078)
  - (489) – Ukawaziswa Trust: Journalism Training, 1986 September-November (Box 105, Folder 1079)
  - (489) – Ukawaziswa Trust: Journalism Training, 1987 April-1988 October (Box 106, Folder 1080)
  - United Nations Association: Citizens for Ocean Law, 1980-1983 (Box 106, Folder 1081)
  - United States-Mexican Relations: Front of File, 1979-1980, 1983 (Box 106, Folder 1082)
  - United States-Mexican Relations, 1978 September-1979 October (Box 106, Folder 1083)
  - United States-Mexican Relations, 1980 January-1981 February (Box 106, Folder 1084)
  - United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (I): Draft Report on Proposed Foundation Guidelines for Supporting Activities Regarding the United States and Mexico, 1980 May (Box 106, Folder 1085)
  - United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (II): Mexico and the Rockefeller Foundation, 1980 February (Box 106, Folder 1086)
  - United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (III): Prospects for Employment Creation in Mexico during the Next Decade: Implications for the Relationship between Mexican Labor Supply and Future Employment Opportunities in the United States, 1979 July (Box 106, Folder 1087)
  - United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (V), 1980 (Box 106, Folder 1088)
  - United States-Mexican Relations: Supplementary Material (V), 1979, no date (Box 107, Folder 1089)
  - University of Arizona: U. S.-Mexico Economic Relations, 1982-1986 (Box 107, Folder 1090)
  - University of California: Latin American and Asian Development: Front of File, 1982, 1984, 1986-1987, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 1091)
  - University of California: Latin American and Asian Development, 1984 January-April (Box 107, Folder 1092)
  - University of California: Latin American and Asian Development, 1984 May-1989 May (Box 107, Folder 1093)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy, 1977-1979, 1984, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 1094)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (I): Conference on International Security and Arms Control, 30 March-1 April 1982 (Box 107, Folder 1095)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (II): "International Arrangements for the Back End of the Nuclear Fuel Cycle", Volume 1, pp. 1-III-67, no date (Box 107, Folder 1096)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (III): "International Arrangements for the Back End of the Nuclear Fuel Cycle", Volume 1, pp. IV-1-VI-54, no date (Box 107, Folder 1097)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (IV): "International Arrangements for the Back End of the Nuclear Fuel Cycle", Volume 2, pp. VII-1-VIII-93, no date (Box 107, Folder 1098)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (V): "International Arrangements for the Back End of the Nuclear Fuel Cycle", Volume 2, pp. IX-1-X-55, no date (Box 108, Folder 1099)
  - University of California, Berkeley: Nuclear Energy: Supplementary Material (VI): "Plutonium, Power, and Politics", International Arrangements for the Disposition of Spent Nuclear Fuel, by Gene I. Rochlin, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 1100)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits: Front of File, 1975, 1978-1979, 1981, 1983 (Box 108, Folder 1101)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits: Evaluation, 1975, 1978, 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 1102)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits, 1974 July-1975 December (Box 108, Folder 1103)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits, 1975 November-1977 December (Box 108, Folder 1104)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits, 1978 March (Box 108, Folder 1105)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits, 1978 March-1982 February (Box 109, Folder 1106)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits: Supplementary Material (I): "The Persian Gulf and the Strait of Hormuz", by R. K. Ramazani, Volume Three, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 1107)
  - University of Delaware: International Straits: Supplementary Material (II): "The Strait of Gibraltar and the Mediterranean", by Scott C. Truver, Volume Four, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 1108)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Front of File, 1974, 1977-1978, 1980, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 1109)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Evaluation, 1977-1978, 1981, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 1110)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1974 February-1975 March (Box 109, Folder 1111)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1975 July-December (Box 109, Folder 1112)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1975 December-1976 December (Box 109, Folder 1113)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1977 January-February (Box 109, Folder 1114)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1977 June-August (Box 110, Folder 1115)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1977 September-December (Box 110, Folder 1116)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 1117)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change, 1979-1981 (Box 110, Folder 1118)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (I), 1977-1979 (Box 110, Folder 1119)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (II): "Climate, Present, Past and Future, Volume 2: Climatic History and the Future", by H. H. Lamb, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 1120)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (III): Climatic Research Unit Annual Reports: Third, Fifth, Seventh, Eighth, Ninth Reports, 1973-1980 (Box 111, Folder 1121)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (IV): "Climate Monitor", Vol. 6, Nos. 3-5, Vol. 7, No. 2, 1977 June-1978 May (Box 111, Folder 1122)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (V): "Historical Weather Mapping Project", Annual Report 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 111, Folder 1123)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (VI): Articles, Lectures, Publications by H. H. Lamb, 1967, 1973-1975 (Box 111, Folder 1124)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (VII), 1974 March-April (Box 111, Folder 1125)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (VIII): School of Environmental Sciences, 1968-1976 (Box 111, Folder 1126)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (IX): Publications, 1968-1970, 1972-1974, no date (Box 111, Folder 1127)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (X): Research Training in the Natural Environmental Sciences, NERC Research Students and Fellows, 1973/74, 1974 May (Box 111, Folder 1128)
  - University of East Anglia: Climate Change: Supplementary Material (XI): "Geographical Patterns of Climatic Change: 1000 BC-1700 AD", by T. M. L. Wigley, 1977 September 26 (Box 111, Folder 1129)
  - University of Ife: African Conference, 1982-1983, 1986-1987 (Box 112, Folder 1130)
  - University of Ife: African Conference: Supplementary Material (I): Papers Presented at the International Conference on Africa and the Great Powers, 1-4 June 1983 (Box 112, Folder 1131)
  - University of Ife: African Conference: Supplementary Material (II): Papers Presented at the International Conference on Africa and the Great Powers, 1-4 June 1983 (Box 112, Folder 1132)
  - University of Ife: African Conference: Supplementary Material (III): Papers Presented at the International Conference on Africa and the Great Powers, 1-4 June 1983 (Box 112, Folder 1133)
  - University of Ife: African Conference: Supplementary Material (IV): "Africa and the Great Powers in the 1980s", edited by Olajide Aluko, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 1134)
  - University of Illinois: Developing Countries Security: Front of File, 1979-1981, 1985-1986 (Box 112, Folder 1135)
  - University of Illinois: Developing Countries Security, 1979 August-1981 May (Box 112, Folder 1136)
  - University of Illinois: Developing Countries Security, 1982 January-1984 May (Box 112, Folder 1137)
  - University of Illinois: Developing Countries Security: "Security Policies of Developing Countries", edited by Edward A. Kolodziej and Robert E. Harkavy, 1982 (Box 113, Folder 1138)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976-1979, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 113, Folder 1139)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales, 1976 August-December (Box 113, Folder 1140)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales, 1977-1978 (Box 113, Folder 1141)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales, 1979, 1981-1984 (Box 113, Folder 1142)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales: Supplementary Material (I): Proposed Book on Arms Sales and Public Accountability, Chapters 1-3, no date (Box 113, Folder 1143)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales: Supplementary Material (II): Proposed Book on Arms Sales and Public Accountability, Chapters 4-6, no date (Box 113, Folder 1144)
  - University of Lancaster: Arms Sales: Supplementary Material (III): Proposed Book on Arms Sales and Public Accountability, Chapters 7-9, no date (Box 113, Folder 1145)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants: Front of File and Evaluation, 1979-1980, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 1146)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants, 1977 January-1979 March (Box 114, Folder 1147)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants, 1979 June-December (Box 114, Folder 1148)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants, 1980-1983 (Box 114, Folder 1149)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants: Supplementary Material (I): "Boundaries: National Autonomy and its Limits", edited by Peter G. Brown and Henry Shue, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 1150)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants: Supplementary Material (II): Working Papers, NB-1, NB-2, NB-3, NB-5, NB-6, 1980 April-1981 April (Box 114, Folder 1151)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants: Supplementary Material (III): "QQ - Report from the Center for Philosophy and Public Policy", Vol. 1, No. 1, Winter 1981; Vol. 2, No 2, Spring 1982; Vol. 2, No. 3, Summer 1982; Vol. 3, No. 1, Winter 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 114, Folder 1152)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants: Supplementary Material (IV), 1981-1983 (Box 114, Folder 1153)
  - University of Maryland: Mexican Migrants: Supplementary Material (V): "The Border That Joins: Mexican Migrants and U. S. Responsibility", edited by Peter G. Brown and Henry Shue, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 1154)
  - University of Maryland: Nuclear Deterrence Conference: Front of File and Evaluation, 1983, 1986, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 1155)
  - University of Maryland: Nuclear Deterrence Conference, 1982 May-1983 January (Box 114, Folder 1156)
  - University of Maryland: Nuclear Deterrence Conference, 1983 February-1984 December (Box 115, Folder 1157)
  - University of Maryland: Nuclear Deterrence Conference: Supplementary Material, 1983-1984 (Box 115, Folder 1158)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations: Front of File and Evaluation, 1976, 1978, 1982-1983 (Box 115, Folder 1159)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations, 1975 October-1976 February (Box 115, Folder 1160)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations, 1976 March-1977 December (Box 115, Folder 1161)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 1162)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations, 1979-1980 (Box 115, Folder 1163)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations, 1981, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 1164)
  - University of Michigan: Soviet-East European Relations: Supplementary Material: "East-West Relations and the Future of Eastern Europe", edited by Morris Bornstein, Zvi Gitelman and William Zimmerman, 1981 (Box 115, Folder 1165)
  - (489) – University of Natal: Built Environment Support Group: Front of File, 1986, 1990-1991 (Box 116, Folder 1166)